question_data = [
    {"text": "A slug's blood is green.", "answer": "True"},
    {"text": "The loudest animal is the African Elephant.", "answer": "False"},
    {"text": "Approximately one quarter of human bones are in the feet.", "answer": "True"},
    {"text": "The total surface area of a human lungs is the size of a football pitch.", "answer": "True"},
    {"text": "In West Virginia, USA, if you accidentally hit an animal with your car, you are free to take it home to eat.", "answer": "True"},
    {"text": "In London, UK, if you happen to die in the House of Parliament, you are entitled to a state funeral.", "answer": "False"},
    {"text": "It is illegal to pee in the Ocean in Portugal.", "answer": "True"},
    {"text": "You can lead a cow down stairs but not up stairs.", "answer": "False"},
    {"text": "Google was originally called 'Backrub'.", "answer": "True"},
    {"text": "Buzz Aldrin's mother's maiden name was 'Moon'.", "answer": "True"},
    {"text": "No piece of square dry paper can be folded in half more than 7 times.", "answer": "False"},
    {"text": "A few ounces of chocolate can to kill a small dog.", "answer": "True"}
]
"""
question_data = [{
    "response_code":0,
    "results":[
        {"category":"General Knowledge",
         "type":"boolean",
         "difficulty":"easy",
         "question":"The Great Wall of China is visible from the moon.",
         "correct_answer":"False",
         "incorrect_answers":["True"]},
        {"category":"General Knowledge","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"Gumbo is a stew that originated in Louisiana.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"General Knowledge","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"Nutella is produced by the German company Ferrero.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"General Knowledge","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"The color orange is named after the fruit.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"General Knowledge","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"You can legally drink alcohol while driving in Mississippi.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"General Knowledge","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"In 2010, Twitter and the United States Library of Congress partnered together to archive every tweet by American citizens.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"General Knowledge","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"The Lego Group was founded in 1932.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"General Knowledge","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"Dihydrogen Monoxide was banned due to health risks after being discovered in 1983 inside swimming pools and drinking water.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"General Knowledge","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"Scotland voted to become an independent country during the referendum from September 2014.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"General Knowledge","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"Ping-Pong originated in England","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]}]}
    ] 
"""